ucables.com 2002-12-03

# Orders > Privacy Policy

At ucables.com, we are committed to protect your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalised shopping experience.   
Our secure servers protect this information using encryption. Your personal information can't be read as it travels to our ordering system. Your information will not be shared or distributed or ever compromised for any reason. Security is at the very core of our business, and we take it very seriously.   
When you conduct a transaction on our web site, we encrypt all your private information. That information is stored on a secure server housed in a secure data center. All transactions are conducted through our secure servers. Our business depends on your trust. We aim at earning your trust by collecting only the minimum amount of information that we need to protect Direct International users (and ourselves) against fraud and by keeping your personal information confidential. Please read on for further details about our privacy policy.   

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

  * When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date. This allows us to process and fulfil your orders and to notify you the status of your order status. 
  * We also ask for your telephone number which enables us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order. For some international deliveries this number may be given to our couriers.. 

**How does uCables.com protect customer information?**   
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before sending it to us. Furthermore, as required by the Spanish Data Protection Acts of 1984 and 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information you have given us, in order to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request at proof of identity before disclosing sensitive information to you. 

**What about "cookies"?**   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features such as store items in your shopping basket between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping basket and purchasing them. 

**Will ucables.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**   
ucables.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. 

**In Summary**   
We are committed to protect your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to do possible shopping at uCables.com and to enhance your over-all shopping experience. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. 

**Your Consent**   
By using our Web site, you consent the collection and use of this information by ucables.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Tell Us What You Think**   
uCables.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please contact with our [Customers Care Department](http://ucables.com/contact.phtml) if you need any further info.
